It's just a little cover-up.
Skincare is a thriller, drama, comedy film directed by Austin Peters.
Famed aesthetician Hope Goldman is about to take her career to the
next level by launching her very own skin care line.
However, she soon faces a new challenge when a rival opens
a boutique directly across from her store.
Suspecting that someone is trying to sabotage her, she embarks on a quest
to unravel the mystery of who's trying to destroy her life.
Hope Goldman, played by Elizabeth Banks.
Jordan, played by Lewis Pullman.
Marine, played by Michaela Jaé Rodriguez.
Angel Vergara, played by Luis Gerardo Méndez.
Brett Wright, played by Nathan Fillion.
Armen, played by Erik Palladino.
Skincare is a 2024 American thriller film directed by Austin Peters in his feature
directorial debut, from a screenplay by Peters, Sam Freilich, and Deering Regan.
Starring Elizabeth Banks, Lewis Pullman, Michaela Jaé Rodriguez, Luis Gerardo Méndez, and Nathan Fillion, the film follows Hope Goldman (Banks), a famed Los Angeles
aesthetician who suspects Angel Vergara (Méndez), a rival aesthetician who opens a boutique directly across from hers, of stalking and harassing her.
With the help of life coach Jordan Weaver (Pullman), the two embark on a quest to uncover
the identity of the blackmailer, save her business, and clear her name.
Skincare was released theatrically in the United
States on August 16, 2024, by IFC Films.
The film explores themes of based on true story, anaesthesia,
business rivalry, revenge thriller, murder for hire.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending and emotional.